[
    {
        "question": "In which country would you most likely find the traditional Mariachi bands?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Turkish city has spread to both sides of the Bosphorus Strait?",
        "answer": "Istanbul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the United Nations (UN) Headquarters located?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 20204, what is the most widely-spoken language in South America?",
        "answer": "Spanish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which South American country is known as the `Land of Poets`?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. state is nicknamed `The Sooner State`?",
        "answer": "Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first picture postcard was invented in which country?",
        "answer": "England"
    },
    {
        "question": "A building called `The Gherkin` graces which city`s skyline?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the least populous country in Africa?",
        "answer": "Seychelles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Eternal Flame Falls?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city did Frank Sinatra help immortalize as `That Toddlin` Town`?",
        "answer": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "question": "By what other name is Lac Leman known?",
        "answer": "Lake Geneva"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two countries share Lake Geneva?",
        "answer": "France and Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the 49th parallel separate Montana from?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the two letter postal abbreviation for the state of Maine?",
        "answer": "ME"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Appalachian Trail runs over 2,000 miles from Maine to what southern state?",
        "answer": "Georgia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Scottish landmark borders on Fort Augustus?",
        "answer": "Loch Ness"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only waterfall on the entire length of the Mississippi River?",
        "answer": "St. Anthony Falls"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only sea without any coasts?",
        "answer": "Sargasso"
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of the River Nile is located in Egypt?",
        "answer": "22%"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the driest place on Earth?",
        "answer": "McMurdo Dry Valleys in Antactica"
    },
    {
        "question": "What African country served as the setting for Tatooine in Star Wars?",
        "answer": "Tunisia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the flattest continent?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country has the most coastline?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find Myra Necropolis",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which small French town holds an annual festival celebrating Mexico?",
        "answer": "Barcelonnette"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country has a national park called the `Valley of Flowers`?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Great Pyramid of Cholula is located in what country?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What famous aqueduct is located in Wales?",
        "answer": "Pontcysyllte Aqueduct and Canal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Richmond is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What monument, located in Washington D.C., was once the tallest structure in the world?",
        "answer": "Washington Monument"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state was named after the King of France?",
        "answer": "Louisiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cincinnati is located on the shores of what river?",
        "answer": "Ohio River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state`s name is derived from the Choctaw Indian word for `red man`?",
        "answer": "Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of Chattanooga is located in which state?",
        "answer": "Tennessee"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two countries once technically fought wars against a species of bird?",
        "answer": "Australia and China"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most densely populated US state?",
        "answer": "New Jersey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national animal of Scotland?",
        "answer": "Unicorn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first foreign country you will reach if you go south from Miami, Florida.",
        "answer": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which beach is trademarked Surf City USA?",
        "answer": "Huntington Beach, California -- Although Hawaii is the birthplace of modern surfing, Huntington Beach in Southern California is trademarked as Surf City USA."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was America`s first boardwalk?",
        "answer": "Atlantic City Boardwalk, New Jersey -- Built in 1870, the original purpose of the boardwalk was to keep sand out of the lobbies of the ritzy beachfront hotels."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continental U.S. state has the most beaches?",
        "answer": "Florida -- Alaska has the most coastline, but Florida has the most beaches. It has 1,350 miles of coastline, which includes 850 miles of beaches."
    },
    {
        "question": "The film `Point Break` was shot at which beach in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "Cannon Beach in Oregon -- It`s not a typical sunny and tropical beach, but the beach is still so cinematically beautiful that film scenes are filmed there."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which countries does France share a land border with?",
        "answer": "Spain, Luxembourg, Belgium, Switzerland, Monaco, Andorra, Germany and Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Luzon and Mindanao are the two largest islands of what country?",
        "answer": "The Philippines"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country is Mt. Ararat located?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island nation was ruled by `Papa Doc` and `Baby Doc` Duvalier?",
        "answer": "Haiti"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the world`s largest lake crossed by the equator?",
        "answer": "Lake Victoria"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is the headquarters for the Mayo Clinic?",
        "answer": "Minnesota"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano `Taal`?",
        "answer": "The Philippines"
    }
]